ello.com 2017-05-15

# Ello Privacy Policy

Privacy policy

Ello receives personal information through this website. You may, for example, submit personal information if you submit a contact form, place an order, or comment on the site in general.

In any case where you provide personal information, we will only use this information the way it is intended - if you place an order, we will only use that information for billing and delivery. We do not sell personal information. We do not store your information on our servers.

This privacy policy only covers ELLO CORPORATION’s website at ello.com

The Ello site does not automatically capture or store personal information, other than logging the user’s IP address and session information, such as the duration of the visit and the type of browser used. This is recognised by the Web server and is only used for system administration and to provide statistics, which we use to evaluate use of the site. We use Google Analytics to track visitor data to our website.

Visitors to our websites

When someone visits www.ello.com we collect standard internet log information and details of visitor behaviour patterns. We do this to find out things such as the number of visitors to the various parts of the site. We will not associate any data gathered from this site with any personally identifying information from any source. If we do want to collect personally identifiable information through our website, we will be up front about this. We will make it clear when we collect personal information and will explain what we intend to do with it.

Newsletter

If you a user submits their email address to our newsletter subscription bar, we will add this address to our mailing list. The mailing list will be regularly sent promotional offers.  
These offers are provided by PEJ.com - only PEJ and ELLO CORPORATION will have access to the email addresses provided. We do not sell or share personal information like email addresses with any other third parties.

Use of cookies

Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer by websites that you visit. They are widely used in order to make websites work, or work more efficiently, as well as to provide information to the owners of the site.

These cookies are used to collect information about how visitors use our site. We use the information to compile reports and to help us improve the site. The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, including the number of visitors to the site, where visitors have come to the site from and the pages they visited.

Most web browsers allow some control of most cookies through the browser settings. To find out more about cookies, including how to see what cookies have been set and how to manage and delete them, visit www.allaboutcookies.org.
